predatornutrition.com 2018-11-18

# Find out more about our Privacy Policy at Predator Nutrition

**Predator Nutrition Privacy Policy**

This Policy outlines the information we collect about the visitors to our website and explains how we use it.

We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy.

**What personal data we collect and how we use it**

_When you place an order with us_ , we collect your name, email address, postal address, phone number and payment details. We need this information to process your order and keep you updated about the progress of it.

We also keep a record of your purchase history, which allows us to improve our products and services and personalise any promotional content, should you opt into receiving it.

We don’t store your card information - it is collected by our third-party payment processors, who specialise in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions.

_When you register for an account_ , we keep a record of your name, your email address and your password, so we can help you log into your account later, if you ever forget your credentials. Having your date of birth would help us improve your shopping experience but this field is fully optional.

**Marketing**

_When you agree to receiving marketing from us_ using a sign-up page or checking the “Email” or “SMS” box, we will save your contact details (email address and / or phone number) together with your communication preferences and only send you marketing via your chosen channel – email and / or SMS.

We will periodically send you promotional emails / SMS about new products, special offers or other events, which we think you may find interesting. Should you wish to stop receiving those updates, you can easily unsubscribe from them following the unsubscribe / opt-out links provided in every communication we send you.

**Controlling your personal information**

We may pass your information to our third-party service providers and other associated organisations for the purposes of completing tasks and providing services to you on our behalf. We will not sell or rent your information to third parties, nor will we share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.

We may use your personal information to send you promotional content which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish for this to happen. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time following the unsubscribe / opt-out links provided in all communications from us. Alternatively, you can do this by emailing us at [support@predatornutrition.com](mailto:support@predatornutrition.com).

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the GDPR. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us at [support@predatornutrition.com](mailto:support@predatornutrition.com) or write to Data Protection Officer, Predator Nutrition, The Light Shopping Centre, The Headrow, Leeds , LS1 8TL.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Data security**

We are committed to ensuring that all data we collect is gathered, stored and processed in accordance with the GDPR. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we hold on you.

We will not sell or rent your information to third parties, nor will we share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest and once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**This site uses cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We do not keep any of your personal details on cookies. We simply store your Customer ID (just a number) in cookie format. This Customer ID does not correlate to any of your personal information. We also store your first name on cookie format to personalise this website. This cookie is only present if you have not registered as a member of our site. If you are a member, then the only cookie that we use is the Customer ID cookie.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our advertising partners Adroll use cookies on this site to improve your website experience and provide you with personalised advertising from this site and other advertisers in the AdRoll's network.

**List of cookies we collect**

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE NAME  COOKIE DESCRIPTION

CART     The association with your shopping cart.

CATEGORY_INFO             Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.

COMPARE           The items that you have in the Compare Products list.

CURRENCY          Your preferred currency

CUSTOMER         An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.

CUSTOMER_AUTH          An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.

CUSTOMER_INFO            An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.

CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS        Stores the Customer Segment ID

EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE  A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.

FRONTEND         You sesssion ID on the server.

GUEST-VIEW      Allows guests to edit their orders.

LAST_CATEGORY              The last category you visited.

LAST_PRODUCT                The most recent product you have viewed.

NEWMESSAGE  Indicates whether a new message has been received.

NO_CACHE         Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.

PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART  A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.

POLL      The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.

POLLN   Information on what polls you have voted on.

RECENTLYCOMPARED    The items that you have recently compared.

STF         Information on products you have emailed to friends.

STORE   The store view or language you have selected.

USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE               Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.

VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS                The products that you have recently viewed.

WISHLIST             An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.

WISHLIST_CNT  The number of items in your Wishlist.
